Look! There's little ducks!
Six little ducks that I once knew,
fat ones, skinny ones, fair ones too.
But the one little duck with the feather on his back,
he led the others with the quack quack quack.
Quack quack quack, quack quack quack.
He led the others with the quack quack quack.
Here we go!
Down to the river they would go.
Wibble wobble, wibble wobble to and fro.
But the one little duck with the feather on his back,
he led the others with the quack quack quack.
Quack quack quack, quack quack quack.
He led the others with the quack quack quack.
Home by the river they would come.
Wibble wobble, wibble wobble ho hum hum.
But the one little duck with the feather on his back,
he led the others with the quack quack quack.
Quack quack quack, quack quack quack.
He led the others with the quack quack quack.
Quack quack quack.
Meow.